bitcomet.com 2019-07-24

# BitComet - BitComet Website Privacy Policy

BitComet official site and its affiliate sites are committed to respecting the privacy rights and concerns of all users of our Sites and Services. As such, we have established and implemented this privacy policy to inform visitors to the Sites and users of the Services how we use and protect the information we collect. 

## 1.What information does BitComet collect?

Our primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide you with the best and most useful content and services. Several of the services and features that we offer on our sites require you to provide us with information as a condition of usage. These include registration of BitComet passport, the ability to post opinions or write blogs, and so on.

We collect personally identifiable information, such as your email address, username, password and gender when you provide it to us. 

## 2\. What is BitComet' practice regarding cookies?

Your Internet browser has a feature called cookies, which stores small amounts of data on your computer about your visit to any of our sites. You do not need to have cookies turned on to visit most of our sites, although active participation in certain areas of our sites may require cookies. Cookies alone tell us nothing about who you are unless you specifically give us personally identifiable information, in which case we use the information to enhance your services in the ways described below. By adjusting your settings on your browser, you may elect not to allow cookies to be collected.

We also use technologies, including electronic images known as Web bugs—sometimes called transparent GIFs, clear GIFs, or beacons—that allow us to track general user-traffic patterns. We also automatically receive and record information from our servers and from your browser, including your IP address, the time of your visit to pages on our site, and information about pages you visited. Unless you have registered for one of our products or services, the information we gather through the use of tracking technologies cannot be matched with any personally identifiable information about you.

We use cookies and tracking technologies in a variety of ways, including:

  * Keeping count of return visits to our site or our advertisers' or partners' sites; 
  * Accumulating and reporting anonymous, aggregate (data collected in mass), statistical information on Web-site and advertisement usage; 
  * Determining which features our overall user population likes best; 
  * Saving your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our sites; 

We allow other companies that are presenting advertisements on our sites. We do not give any personally identifiable information to them as part of this relationship. Unless you visit the Web site of these companies and provide them with personally identifiable information about yourself, these tracking technologies tell those advertisers nothing about who you are. Our advertisers' use of tracking technology is subject to their own privacy policies.

## 3\. How does BitComet use the information?

We use the information we gather for four general purposes:

  * To customize the advertising and the content you see; 
  * To enhance the user experience in our network of sites. We use tracking information to determine how well each page performs overall based on aggregate user demographics and traffic patterns to those pages. This helps us continue to build a better service for you; 
  * To send you information you agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to you. 

## 4\. How does BitComet share the information?

**Personally identifiable information**

We will make your personally identifiable information available to other companies or people when:

  * You volunteer information or create a public profile in the course of your participation in our community features such as user opinions and reviews. 
  * When required by law, such as when we respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process. 
  * We believe that your actions violate applicable laws, BitComet Terms of Use, or any usage guidelines for specific products or services, or threaten the rights, property, or safety of our company, our users, or others.

**Aggregate information**

We aggregate personally identifiable information and disclose such information in a non-personally identifiable manner to advertisers and other third parties for marketing, promotional, and other purposes. We do not disclose to these entities any information that could be used to identify you personally.

## 5\. What are my options?

Users who would rather not provide any of the user data requested by our registration process do not need to register with us. You can still view much of the content and use many of the services offered by our sites without registering.

## 6\. How can I review and update my personally identifiable information?

You can review, correct, or change the information collected during registration for any of our sites. The instructions for doing this can be found in our member-services areas. Users may change information at any time and as often as necessary. 

## 7\. How about Third-party Comapny?

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website.

## 8\. How will I know if the privacy policy is changed?

Any modifications to our privacy practices will be reflected first within this area of our network of Web sites. If there is a material change in our privacy practices, we will indicate on our sites that our privacy practices have changed and provide a link to the new privacy statement.

Revised by BitComet Development Group on May 16, 2018
